DALIA ELNAGGAR

E: daliadodo019@gmail.com | T: +201112795720 | Obour City-Cairo, LinkedIn Account

Certified Management Accountant (CMA Holder)

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

As a distinguished Certified Management Accountant (**CMA**) and a proactive member of the Institute of Management Accountants (**IMA**), I offer a solid grounding in accounting and finance. I am in pursuit of a stimulating role that will enable me to apply my skills and experience, thereby contributing significantly to a company's financial growth and success.

Knowledge in:

- General Ledger Accounting
- Cash Management
- Month and Year-end Close

- Project Accounting and Cost Allocation
- Fixed Asset Accounting
- Accounting process improvement

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Majid Al Futtaim

September 2023 – Present

S2P ASSOCIATE ACCOUNTANT

- Maintain all vendor accounts within payment terms and company policy.
- Ensured that submitted **payment requests** by various departments for supplier are in line with the governing policies & procedures.
- Monitor Aging Vendor on a Monthly Basis .
- Addressed, Managed & Resolved supplier Queries.
- Oversaw Assigned Vendor Account Reconciliations and Necessary Follow up Action .

kitchen &CO

July 2023 – September 2023

GENERAL ACCOUNTANT

Served as General accountant for approximately all accounting and financial departments AP, AR,
 Treasury & Bank accountant also prepared some analysis (Cost & Aging) reports and reported it to the Decision makers.

Decorative Class & Arab Union Glass.

April 2022 – October 2022

FINANCIAL ACCOUNTANT

- Preparing **Financial Reports** related to AR, AP & Banking and treasury Sections.
- Compiled **Accounts Receivable** Aging Reports and Visualizing it into Dynamic Charts & Analyzing Monthly Income Statement into Common Size analysis.
- Served as **AP Accountant** for short time: Reconciled the petty cash of purchasing Clerks & Followed up the payments of the Vendors.

DALIA ELNAGGAR Page 2

Luminous Company. July 2021 – April 2022

COST ACCOUNTANT

• Prepared and completed **internal cost audits**. Complied with Generally Accepted Accounting Principles **(GAAP)** for financial statements.

• Planned and recorded variable costs (e.g. purchases of raw material and operations costs).

EDUCATION

- Faculty of Commerce (Accounting Section). Ain Shams University, 2016:2020
 Grade: Good
- Institute of Management Accountants (IMA), 2020: 2023

COURSE AND CERTIFICATES

CMA (Certified Management Accountant), ATC Croup, 2020 – 2021

OTHER RELEVANT INFORMATION

- Languages: English (Fluent).
- Computer Skills: Microsoft Office, Excel for Accounting, Internet Advanced Search.
- **Technical Skills:** MS Excel (Advanced User: Pivot Tables + VLOOKUP), data management abilities, Independent research, Budget skills, Financial statement analysis & Dashboard visualization skills.